airdropalert.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Statement | AirdropAlert

Version control last updated version 18 February, 2018

### 1 Introduction

This privacy statement will inform you as user of our website and services (hereinafter also referred to as "you") which personal data AirdropAlert.com (hereinafter also referred to as "we" and also referred to as "website") collects and processes. Personal data means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person. AirdropAlert.com (the natural person behind www.AirdropAlert.com) can be regarded as "controller" of your personal data according to the applicable data protection law. This means that AirdropAlert.com determines which personal data will be processed, which means are used for the processing of such personal data and what the purposes are for the processing of your personal data.

We are responsible for the protection of your personal data and therefore ensure that your personal data will be processed in accordance with the applicable data protection law.

### 2 The purpose of processing your personal data

The purpose of processing and collecting your personal data via our website is to ensure that you are able to make use of the services we provide via AirdropAlert.com. We process and collect your personal data in order to inform you about cryptocurrency airdrops. In order to inform you about cryptocurrency airdrops we use your personal data for e-mail marketing activities. We use your personal data to send you a newsletter by e-mail with the purpose of informing you about cryptocurrency airdrops and cryptocurrency airdrops that will be hosted by AirdropAlert.com. In addition we may occasionally use your personal data to promote a bounty for an Initial Coin Offering or an Initial Coin Offering itself by e-mail. A bounty may generally be defined as a reward in the form of a coin or token. This reward in the form of a token is received after you fulfil a small task or complete a small project for the company that is launching the Initial Coin Offering. We may contact you to inform you of new services we will be providing, or events or articles we think will be of interest to you.

We may use your Personal Data to contact you regarding fundraising, support or to inform you of airdrops or Initial Coin Offerings.

We may use your Personal Data internally to help us improve our services and to help resolve any problems.

### 3 The legal ground for processing your personal data

AirdropAlert.com must base the collection and processing of your personal date on the legal grounds as set forth in the applicable data protection law. The legal ground for collecting and processing your personal data is based on your consent for processing and collecting your personal data for the purposes as outlined in section two of this privacy statement. You have the right to withdraw your consent for processing and collecting your personal data for the purposes as outlined in section 2 of this privacy statement at any time. Please note that your withdrawal of your consent for collecting and processing your personal data will not affect the lawfulness of processing your personal data based on your consent before your withdrawal of your consent.

If you do not consented to the collection and processing of your personal data you should refrain from using AirdropAlert.com and the services that are provided on AirdropAlert.com.

You will be provided with the possibility to unsubscribe from our newsletter by e-mail: [support@airdropalert.com](mailto:support@airdropalert.com).

### 4 The personal data we may collect and process

We may collect and process the following personal data in order to inform you about cryptocurrency airdrops

  1. Email address 
  2. Name 
  3. IP address 
  4. Phone number
  5. Wallet address (in case an Ethereum address is considered as personal date in accordance with the applicable date protection law)
  6. Social media
  7. KYC information

Your personal data is only kept for as long as this justified for the purposes for collection and processing your personal data. The purpose for the collection and processing of your personal data is set forth in section 2 of this privacy statement. In addition your personal data is kept for as long as it is needed to comply with applicable legislation and regulations.

If you join the exclusive airdrops of [airdropalert.com](https://airdropalert.com/) or other airdrops hosted by airdropalert.com,you will automatically sign up for the newsletter of airdropalert.com and the newsletter of the Initial Coin Offering you will join via [airdropalert.com](https://airdropalert.com/). Data submitted on the exclusive airdrop forms will be shared with the Initial Coin Offering that offers the airdrop.

Data may be shared with third parties.

### 5 Your rights with regard to your personal data

On the basis of the applicable data protection law you have several rights with regard to your personal data. The rights with regard to your personal data are explicitly defined in the applicable data protection law and are as follows:

  1. You have the right to access your personal data;
  2. You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data;
  3. You have the right to withdraw your consent for the processing of your personal data;
  4. You have the right of rectification or erasure of your personal data;
  5. You have the right of restriction of the processing of your personal data(in some cases); 
  6. You have the right to lodge a complaint with a Data Protection Authority;
  7. You have the right to data portability.

The right to data portability is your right to receive your personal data that you provided to us in a structured and commonly used format and the right to transmit such data to another "controller". The definition of "controller" is set forth in applicable data protection law. We will not hinder you if you want to transmit your personal data. If it is technically possible we will transmit your personal data directly to another controller at your request.

If you wish to exercise your rights with regard to your personal data please let us know. We can be reached by email: [support@airdropalert.com](mailto:support@airdropalert.com). 

### 6 Is the provision of your personal data obligatory or optional?

In order to make use of our services you should at least provide your email address. If you do not provide your email address you cannot make use of our services and you will not be informed about cryptocurrency airdrops via email. You are not obliged to provide your name to us in order to make use of our services. The provision of your name is therefore optional. If you are not willing to provide your personal data you should refrain from using the website and the services of the website.

### 7 The recipients of your personal data

Your personal data will not be disclosed or made available to third parties. However there is an exceptional case in which your personal data may be disclosed or made available to third parties. Your personal data may be disclosed or made available to third parties in order to be compliant with legal obligations, in case a court order, subpoena or similar investigative demand requires us to do so or in case we received a request for cooperation from any law enforcement or other governmental body.

### 8 Identity

Your personal data is collected and processed by airdropalert.com.  
Website: <https://airdropalert.com/>  
Mail: [support@airdropalert.com](mailto:support@airdropalert.com)  
Natural person: M.Christensen  
Entity: AirdropAlert BV, Schiedamse Vest 154, 3011 BH, Rotterdam, The Netherlands

### 9 Security measures

AirdropAlert.com is aware of the importance of the protection of personal data and the applicable data protection law and regulation and will exert its best efforts to take reasonable steps to ensure an appropriate level of protection of your personal data. AirdropAlert.com makes use of Hypertext Transfer Protocol Secure to ensure a secure communication and ensure that no unauthorized third parties are able to access the communication between you and the website. It is important to point out that the security of the transmission of personal data over the internet or the storage of personal data will never be fully guaranteed. We cannot guarantee that the personal data your transmit via our website is fully secure.

### 10 Questions

If you have further questions or if you require further information about this privacy statement do not hesitate to contact us. We can be reached by email: [support@airdropalert.com](mailto:support@airdropalert.com).

### 11 Opt-Out choice

If you do not wish to receive information from us and want to be removed from our email list and database [unsubscribe here](https://airdropalert.com/unsubscribe).

### 12 Updates and changes of the privacy statement

Please keep in mind that we reserve the right to update or change his privacy statement at any time. When this privacy statement is updated or changed we will post the updated or changed privacy statement on our website. We strongly advise you to consult AirdropAlert.com regularly in order to stay informed about the most recent updates and changes of this privacy statement.
